Right.
Just to summarize, bring it all together.
This whole section has been all about loops and how important loops are.
We started looking at why you have loops, and then we look specifically at for loops and how for loops
operate across a certain range.
Normally a specifiable range x equals one to 400 or 50 or whatever it might be.
And then we moved on to look at while loops and how they are a specific example or a specific instantiation
of for loops, because they allow you to operate until a condition is true.
And we looked at how that can be useful if you are unsure of when that condition is going to be true.
We also then saw how you could expand on that, and you could include breaks in your loops, so you
could actually break out of a loop if something happened to be true.
And we used that to even extract all the vowels that were typed into a string into a sentence.
And then we finally just finished off by saying, while loops can be lots of fun, you can even use
them visually with turtle graphics, as you can see here on the screen.
So you can have a lot of fun with them.
So loops really are one of the building blocks, the key building blocks in programming.
So it is important to get your mind around them to understand them.
The more you play with them, the more you will get to understand them and they'll make a lot of sense.
So that's loops very important section.
Hope you enjoyed it.
Keep on practicing and keep on having fun.